makeplayingcards.com 2019-12-29

# MakePlayingCards.com Privacy Policy

This policy covers how MakePlayingCards.com, handles your personal information. At MPC, we are committed to protecting your data and privacy. This privacy policy describes our dedication in protecting our visitors and customers information collected on our website ([www.makeplayingcards.com](https://www.makeplayingcards.com/)). In the policy set herein, "personal and account information" means your name, company name, account number, address, telephone number, and e-mail address plus other information that identifies you. We will not sell any of your personal and account information to third parties.

## What information do we collect when you browse our website

By creating an account at MPC, we need to collect your personal information such as your address, phone number, email address, product selections, the images and texts uploaded for personalized products, delivery address. We also need your Billing Information such as credit card number, billing address, and 3rd party personal information under shipping address to process your orders and requests. If you are using our MarketPlace to sell and share your designs, we will also collect information such as designers name, shop name, the shop's short summary, the shop's full description when customer setup the shop space.

This information might be shared internally in our company to assist with orders and you may also provide personal information about other people, such as their name and physical address. The information is only used for the sole purpose of completing your request or for whatever reason it may have been provided.

We also collect your IP address to measure our web traffic to help provide a relevant shopping experience for you. If you come to our Website via another link, we collect the location of the link that referred you to our website for our own marketing information. We collect information about the browser you are using to help optimize our website experience and we keep track of the pages you visit to help provide you with a more personalized shopping experience.

## 1\. Who is collecting it and how is it collected?

MakePlayingCards.com collects your personal information and data through the following actions:

  * Registration
  * Logout
  * Participating in promotion
  * Ticketing
  * Setup customer Shop Space
  * Contact us
  * Cookies

_Cookies and Tracking Technologies_

Technologies such as: cookies, beacons, tags and scripts are used by MakePlayingCards.Com and analytics. These technologies are used in analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We may receive reports based on the use of these technologies by these companies on an individual as well as aggregated basis.

We use cookies to remember users' settings and activities on our site (e.g. last visited, shopping cart items). Users can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some features or areas of our site may be limited.

_Behavioral Targeting / Re-Targeting_

We partner with a third party to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use technologies such as cookies to gather information about your activities on this site and other sites in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests.

## Log Files

As is true of most web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data. We use this information in order to provide you a relevant and more personalized shopping experience.

We do not link this automatically collected data to other information we collect about you

## 2\. Why is data collected and how will it be used?

We need to collect your personal data and information for the following reasons:

  * provide customer services and product information;
  * process orders that you have submitted;
  * obligate the contract;
  * keep records to maintain customer relationship;
  * data analysis on marketing;
  * surveying;
  * notify the changes of our services to you;
  * for campaigns, fundraising appeals and promotions;

The information you provide us is used in assisting us for reasons such as, processing your orders, maintaining your account at MakePlayingCards.Com and the shipping process.

## 3\. Who will it be shared with? 

MakePlayingCards.Com will share your personal and payment information; with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. We will never sell your personal and payment information to third parties.

  * Service Providers

We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as shipping your order, processing orders or offering customer service. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

  * Legal Disclaimer

We may also disclose your personal information:

    * as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
    * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request,
    * if MakePlayingCards.Com is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information,
    * to any other third party with your prior consent to do so.

## Local Storage Objects (Flash and HTML5):

We use Local Storage Objects (LSO) such as Flash cookies, and Local Storage, such as HTML5 to store content information and preferences. Third parties with whom we partner to provide certain features on our site or to display advertising based upon your Web browsing activity use HTML 5 to collect and store information. Various browsers may offer their own management tools for removing HTML5. To manage Flash cookies, please click here:

<https://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html>

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. All of our servers operate under 128-bit encryption technology and Secure Socket Layers ("SSL") in all areas where your personal and account payment information is required. Our Web site is certified by VeriSign, which verifies that our Web site is authentic and that we use SSL security. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at [enquiry@makeplayingcards.com](mailto:enquiry@makeplayingcards.com)

## Additional Information

_Links to 3rd Party Sites_

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of MakePlayingCards.Com. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy policies. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy policy of any Web site you visit.

_Referrals_

If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend's name and email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site. MakePlayingCards.Com will store this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program.

Your friend may contact us at [enquiry@makeplayingcards.com](mailto:enquiry@makeplayingcards.com) to request that we remove this information from our database.

_Testimonials_

We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our site in addition to other endorsements. With your consent we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [enquiry@makeplayingcards.com](mailto:enquiry@makeplayingcards.com).

_Public Member Directory_

We will list you in our publicly accessible member directory. If you wish to request removal of your information from our directory, you can contact us at [enquiry@makeplayingcards.com](mailto:enquiry@makeplayingcards.com).

_Social Media Widgets_

Our Web site includes Social Media Features, such as the Facebook Like button and Widgets, such as the Share this button. These Features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the Feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Site. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

_Single Sign-On_

You can log in to our site using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form. Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

## Children's Privacy

We are committed to protecting children's online privacy. Our website is intended for users ages 13 and older only. Accordingly, we do not knowingly or intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a user is under the age of 13 and has registered, we will remove their personal information from our database.

## Changes To This Policy

We may update this privacy policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

## User Access and Choice

If your personal information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, amend, delete/remove, or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [enquiry@makeplayingcards.com](mailto:enquiry@makeplayingcards.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. We will respond to your request to access within 30 days.

We will retain your information for as long as your account active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

## Contact Us

MakePlayingCards.Com

**US Hotline:** 888-474-1832

**APAC Hotline:** (852) 2210-1388

## When you contact us in writing

When you submit questions, e-mails, survey, comments, suggestions, reviews, sign up for our mailing list or other written information to us you grant MakePlayingCards.Com and its affiliates permission to use, share, implement, transfer such information for internal use, marketing, advertising and other promotional purposes. MakePlayingCards.Com will not sell or share your information collected to a 3rd party. If you do not wish to receive promotional information, you may opt out of future communications by clicking here and unsubscribing to our e-mail subscriptions.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy please contact us here: [enquiry@makeplayingcards.com](mailto:enquiry@makeplayingcards.com)
